unifii.io 2019-10-17

# Unifii Corporation LLP Privacy Policy

updated August 2019                                                   Unifii Corporation Privacy Policy
Unifii Corporation LLP Privacy Policy
You have entered a “replicated website” of an Independent Affiliate for Unifii Corporation LLP
(referred to herein as “Unifii Corporation”, “our”, “us” or “we”) or through our corporate site
unifii.io. These sites are operated by Unifii Corporation, and are hosted on the server of Unifii
Corporations’ third-party technology provider. The information you submit on the site is sent to
and accessed by Unifii Corporation, as well as the Independent Contractor (referred to herein
as “Affiliate” or “Preferred Member”) to whom this Site is assigned (except as set forth in this
privacy policy). By visiting this Site and providing information to Unifii Corporation you consent to
the following privacy policy, use and disclosure of information.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
Unifii Corporation is the sole owner of the information collected on our websites and on the
replicated websites that we provide for use by our Affiliates and Preferred Members (hereafter
the “websites”). We collect information from customers and visitors to the websites at different
points on the websites.
Personally Identifiable Information
Through your use of or visits to our websites, you may be required or requested to provide
personally identifiable information to us. Personally identifiable information is any piece of
information that can potentially be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person
including names, addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers, and credit card or banking
information.
Customer Information
Customers are required to provide contact information (such as name, mailing address,
telephone number(s), and email address). Customers are also required to provide payment
information (such as credit card, debit card, or checking account information). We use this
information to maintain contact with customers, to process customer orders, and for billing
purposes.
Profile Information
Unifii Corporation gathers and stores some information that it collects through cookies, log files,
clear gifs, and/or third parties. Such information is not used to provide offers or create a profile of
visitors to our websites (“users”) which include visitors and customers. Profile information is not
tied to a user’s personally identifiable information, however, such information is aggregated to
provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user.
INFORMATION USE & SHARING
Personally Identifiable Information
Unifii Corporation DOES NOT share personally identifiable information except with contracted
service providers as may be necessary to: (a) process orders and/or returns and obtain
payment; (b) complete an enrolment as a customer. We also provide personally identifiable
information: (a) to up-line Affiliate(s) as described herein; and/or (b) to the Affiliate on the
Company’s Affiliate locator feature on the Company’s website; and/or (c) to assign a sales or
enrolment lead to an active Affiliate.
Genealogy Information
Unifii Corporation provides certain information to Affiliates regarding Customers enrolled in an
Affiliate’s downline marketing organization. As a Customer of Unifii Corporation, your name,
address, email address, telephone number, sales volume, and order history information will be
v0819                                                                                      Page 1 of 3

updated August 2019                                                     Unifii Corporation Privacy Policy
provided to other Affiliates as downline genealogy information. No other personally identifiable
information will be shared with other Affiliates. Information relating to downline Affiliates is made
available to Affiliates subject to a confidentiality and non-solicitation covenant in the
independent distributor agreement that each Affiliate enters into with Unifii Corporation.
However, Unifii Corporation does not warrant that other Affiliates will adhere to the
confidentiality and non-solicitation covenants, and Unifii Corporation shall not be responsible for
Affiliates’ violation of these covenants.
Sales Information
If you make a purchase from an Affiliate through this Site, we will provide the Affiliate to whom
this Site is assigned with your name, contact information, a description of the item(s) purchased,
and the sales volume associated with the purchase. No other personally identifiable information
will be shared with the Affiliates.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
Unifii Corporation may share aggregated demographic information with our partners, vendors,
suppliers, third party providers, and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable
information.
Business Transitions
In the event Unifii Corporation goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being
acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, the personal information of
customers and Affiliates will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. If as a result of
the business transition, a customer’s personally identifiable information will be used in a manner
different from that stated at the time of collection, the customer will be given a choice
consistent with our notification of changes section.
Lead Assignment and AffiliateLocator Features
Unifii Corporation occasionally will assign prospective sales and new customer leads to Affiliates.
In these cases, we will provide the Affiliates the name and contact information of the customer
or prospective customer. In addition, Unifii Corporation has an Affiliate Locator feature on its
website. Pursuant to this feature, a prospective customer can locate a nearby Affiliate. In order
to make the Affiliate Locator feature and the lead assignments effective, the company will
provide the prospective customer with the Affiliates’s name and contact information, which
may include his/her telephone number, address, and/or email address.
COMMUNICATIONS FROM US
Special Offers and Updates
Unifii Corporation sends all Customers a welcoming email to verify password, username, and
reference to terms and agreements signed for during the purchase process. All Customers will
occasionally receive information on the Unifii Corporation business, products, services, special
deals, and a newsletter.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For
instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send customers an
email. Generally, customers may not opt-out of these communications, though they can
deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
Customer Support
Unifii Corporation communicates with Customers via email, regular mail, support ticketing system
and telephone on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating
to their Unifii Corporation services. Such communications may be by email, regular mail, support
v0819                                                                                       Page 2 of 3

updated August 2019                                                  Unifii Corporation Privacy Policy
ticketing system or telephone. Unifii Corporation also communicates with customers by posting
messages in the member site and through its mobile app.
MISCELLANEOUS
Legal Disclaimer
Though Unifii Corporation makes every effort to preserve user privacy, Unifii Corporation may
need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith
belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a law
enforcement action, a subpoena, warrant, court order or legal process served on Unifii
Corporation.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Unifii Corporation reserves the right to amend or change this Privacy Policy at any time at its sole
discretion. When material changes or amendments are made to the Privacy Policy, we will
announce the same at our home page for a period of at least 30 days prior to implementation
of the amended Privacy Policy.
Choice
Users are notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties (with the
exception of IT providers, merchant services providers, and Google Analytics). We do this so
users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that
require an outside party.
Links
Unifii Corporation’ websites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Unifii
Corporation is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage users
to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every
website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to
information collected by Unifii Corporation websites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance
with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal
information to outside parties without your consent.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection
Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our
website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our websites and not to
information collected offline.
Questions
Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to:
compliance@unifii.io
Effective Date
The effective date of this Privacy Policy is May 1, 2018
v0819                                                                                    Page 3 of 3
